The truth is in the music.
Let It Shine is a family, music, tv movie film directed by Paul Hoen.
A young teenage rapper must use his musical talent to help his friend out and win the girl of his dreams by going through
several events of betrayal, trust and agreement while his religious parents have strictly dislike his interests.
Cyrus, played by Tyler James Williams.
Roxxie, played by Coco Jones.
Kris, played by Trevor Jackson.
Lord of Da Bling, played by Brandon Mychal Smith.
Gail, played by Dawnn Lewis.
Levi, played by Alex Désert.
Let It Shine is a 2012 American musical television
film that premiered on Disney Channel.
It features an ensemble cast of Tyler James Williams, Coco
Jones, Trevor Jackson and Brandon Mychal Smith.
The film follows a shy, talented rapper and musician who pens romantic hip hop verses only to stand idly by as they're delivered
to the girl of his dreams by his best friend, in a retelling of Edmond Rostand's 1897 play Cyrano de Bergerac.
The film was directed by Paul Hoen and written by Eric Daniel and Don D.
The Disney Channel Original Movie premiered on June 15, 2012 in the United States
and Canada, and July 20, 2012 in the United Kingdom and Ireland.
The film explores themes of hip-hop, rapper, musical.